<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Craps</string>
    <string name="defaultMoney">$0.00</string>
    <string name="buyButton">BUY</string>
    <string name="rollButton">ROLL</string>
    <string name="homeButton">HOME</string>
    <!--Constants-->
    <string name="saveFileName">craps_save.dat</string>
    <!--Content descriptors-->
    <!--<string name="Background">table</string>-->
    <string name="totalBetLabel">Total bet</string>
    <string name="totalWinsLabel">Total Wins</string>
    <string name="mainTableDescription">A craps table</string>
    <string name="settingsButtonDescription">Settings</string>
    <string name="chip1description">A chip worth $1</string>
    <string name="chip5description">A chip worth $5</string>
    <string name="chip10description">A chip worth $10</string>
    <string name="chip25description">A chip worth $25</string>
    <string name="chip50description">A chip worth $50</string>
    <string name="chip100description">A chip worth $100</string>
    <string name="chip500description">A chip worth $500</string>
    <string name="oddsTableDescription">A table for mincraps</string>
    <string name="dicedesc">The result of the last dice roll</string>

    <!--Strings for tutorial-->
    <string name="t_dice">Dice\n\n
        This is where dice rolls will be displayed after clicking the "Roll" button.</string>
    <string name="t_passline">Passline\n\n
        This is the main Craps bet. You bet on the passline before the point comes out. \nIf the point gets rolled again, you win your bet here.</string>
    <string name="t_dontPass">Don\'t Pass\n\n
        A bet can be placed on Don\'t Pass before the point comes out. If a 7 is rolled before the point is rolled again, you win your bet here.</string>
    <string name="t_sidebet">Side Bet\n\n
        At any point you can bet that one of these numbers gets rolled before a 7 next comes up. If the number comes up, you win your bet.</string>
    <string name="t_buy">Buy Bets\n\n
        Here you bet that the bought value will turn up before a seven. This bet gives true odds, minus a 5% \'vigorish\' that goes to the house.
        \nThe odds of rolling any of these bets is displayed on the board.</string>
    <string name="t_lay">Lay Bets\n\n
        Here you are betting that a 7 will come up before this number. This bet pays true odds, minus a 5% \'vigorish\' for the house.
        \nThe odds of rolling any of these bets is displayed on the board.</string>
    <string name="t_come">Come\n\n
        After the point comes out, you can have a second bet going at the same time.\n
        The next point that gets rolled, your come bet moves to that point. This bet will be paid out if that number comes up before a 7.</string>
    <string name="t_dontCome">Don\'t Come\n\n
        Your bet on this region gets moved to the next point that gets rolled. \n
        If a 7 gets rolled before this point, you win your bet. If the number comes up again before a 7, you lose your bet.</string>
    <string name="t_big6">Big 6\n\n
        When you bet here, the next time a 6 gets rolled, you get your bet doubled. If a 7 comes up before that, you lose your bet.</string>
    <string name="t_big8">Big 8\n\n
        When you bet here, the next time a 8 gets rolled, you get your bet doubled. If a 7 comes up before that, you lose your bet.</string>
    <string name="t_field">Field\n\n
        At any time you can bet on the field. If any of the numbers shown gets rolled (2,3,4,9,10,11,12) before a 7, you win your bet.\n
        In the case of a 2, your profit is doubled. In the case of a 12, your profit is tripled.\n
        If you do not win your field bet on the next roll, then it is lost.</string>

</resources>
